<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/sebek_blog/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/sebek_blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-06-02T15:10:37+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/sebek_blog/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Sebek</title><subtitle>The map, but not the territory:</subtitle><author><name>Sebek</name></author><entry><title type="html">Cardano has to wait</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/sebek_blog/general/2021/06/02/Cardano-has-to-wait/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Cardano has to wait" /><published>2021-06-02T07:57:16+02:00</published><updated>2021-06-02T07:57:16+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/sebek_blog/general/2021/06/02/Cardano-has-to-wait</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/sebek_blog/general/2021/06/02/Cardano-has-to-wait/">&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-beginnings---take-two&quot;&gt;The beginnings - take two.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Actually, I wanted to talk about a blockchain technology,  specifically Cardano. As for now, I am going to postpone it and work on this blog. Up ‘till now I changed the theme to lanyon from minima and uploaded it to GitHubPages. It doesn’t sound like a lot of work, but boy o boy, I am not a gifted webdeveloper at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyways, today I am revising how to perform an abdominal ultrasound correctly. This seemingly basic procedure has its difficulties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for my technical learning project, today is the beginning of my edx Course “ Introduction to programming with Python”. I am super psyched and can’t wait to dive deeper into this subject.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sebek</name></author><category term="general" /><category term="randomThoughts" /><summary type="html">The beginnings - take two. Actually, I wanted to talk about a blockchain technology, specifically Cardano. As for now, I am going to postpone it and work on this blog. Up ‘till now I changed the theme to lanyon from minima and uploaded it to GitHubPages. It doesn’t sound like a lot of work, but boy o boy, I am not a gifted webdeveloper at all. Anyways, today I am revising how to perform an abdominal ultrasound correctly. This seemingly basic procedure has its difficulties. As for my technical learning project, today is the beginning of my edx Course “ Introduction to programming with Python”. I am super psyched and can’t wait to dive deeper into this subject.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">First Blogpost</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/sebek_blog/general/2021/06/01/First-Blogpost/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="First Blogpost" /><published>2021-06-01T21:54:16+02:00</published><updated>2021-06-01T21:54:16+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/sebek_blog/general/2021/06/01/First-Blogpost</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/sebek_blog/general/2021/06/01/First-Blogpost/">&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-beginnings&quot;&gt;The beginnings&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was searching for a solution to start a blog, but I really disliked wordpress. Eventually I came across jekyll as a static site generator. This is my first try and I am far from happy with the results. I tried to change themes and got a bunch of error - messages. Stackoverflow did not have a sneaky solutation for this matter either. 
So the basic minima theme it is. But hey, it is slim, clean and … it works !!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow I start rambling about Cardano and what I have learned so far. Stay tuned.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sebek</name></author><category term="general" /><category term="randomThoughts" /><summary type="html">The beginnings I was searching for a solution to start a blog, but I really disliked wordpress. Eventually I came across jekyll as a static site generator. This is my first try and I am far from happy with the results. I tried to change themes and got a bunch of error - messages. Stackoverflow did not have a sneaky solutation for this matter either. So the basic minima theme it is. But hey, it is slim, clean and … it works !! Tomorrow I start rambling about Cardano and what I have learned so far. Stay tuned.</summary></entry></feed>